I'm taking you in.
如果有必要的话
By force, if necessary.
我会用武力 带你走
Oh, wittle wombax with a wittle gun!
Oh 是一把带拳击手套的威尔特枪
Huh.
嗯
Qwark, stop! You don't want to do this!
夸克 住手  你不能这样做
Don't tell me what I want to do!
别告诉我该怎么做
On your left, Ratchet. Now your right.
在你的左边  瑞奇 现在在右边
Huh?
嗯
Enough, Qwark!
够了 夸克
Whoa!
哦
Nefarious is tricking you! He wants you to destroy the entire system!
博士他在欺骗你 他想要你摧毁整个星系
Oh, that's right, you know everything.
Oh 没错  你知道的真多
Uh-oh!
啊哦
Hey, why don't we all
just listen to Ratchet?
嘿  为什么你就不能乖乖听我的话 瑞奇
Ratchet, look out!
瑞奇  小心
Whoa!
哦
Oh, my.
Oh 我的
Buzz Blades? I taught
you better than that!
弹射刀片  我教你的话会更好
Some of it got in my mouth! It's in my mouth!
有一些进我嘴里了 在我的嘴里
He's just too good.
他好厉害